otogoldmine.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy

**OTOGoldMine.com PRIVACY POLICY**

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you…and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

  * We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address, credit card number or any other information to anyone.

  * We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users.

**NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or when you download free software, enter a contest, order email newsletters or join a limited-access premium site. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.

  * To help you quickly find software, services or information.

  * To help us create content most relevant to you.

  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited".

**CONSENT**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of OTOGoldMine.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" products, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited".

"Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" occasionally allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services, using postal mail only. If you do not want to receive these offers, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing materials from third parties.

**ACCESS**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at the Visitor Center. There, you can:

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us.

  * Tell us whether you want us to send you marketing information, or whether you want third parties to send you their offers by postal mail.

  * Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products.

  * Register. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on OTOGoldMine.com, your information stays with you.

**SECURITY**

"Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We guarantee your e-commerce transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you place orders or access your personal account information, you're utilizing a secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.

In addition, your transactions are guaranteed under the Fair Credit Billing Act. This Act states that your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 in fraudulent credit card charges. If your bank does hold you liable for $50.00 or less, we'll cover your liability provided the unauthorized, fraudulent use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own and from purchases made from us over our secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

"Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in India or any other country where "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited", its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. OTOGoldMine.com encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer:

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.

Check out the FTC's site:  
[ http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html)  for more tips on  
protecting children's privacy online.

**ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by clicking [HERE](http://www.otogoldmine.com/support/), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

**ELECTRONIC PRODUCT REGISTRATION**

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we merge your registration information with any information you've already left with us (we call that information your personal profile). If you haven't previously registered with us, we create a personal profile for you from your product registration information. If you ever want to review or update that information, you can visit the Profile Center, click on Update Profile, and edit any of the Personal Information in your profile. If you haven't already created a Registration ID, we will ask you to do so. This ensures that only you can access your information.

**CUSTOMER PROFILES**

As mentioned above, every registered customer has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification number, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile.

When you register, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code. This code is uniquely yours. It is your passport to seamless travel across OTOGoldMine.com, allowing you to download free software, order free newsletters, and visit premium sites without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won't have to re-register – just use your Registration ID to identify yourself.

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time. For your convenience, we do save billing information in case you want to order from us again, but we don't use this information again without your permission.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

"Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited" and its family of Websites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of "Kanishka Infocom Private Limited", its Websites, or the public.

**AFFILIATED SITES, LINKED SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

OTOGoldMine.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a OTOGoldMine.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through OTOGoldMine.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. OTOGoldMine.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. OTOGoldMine.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of OTOGoldMine.com and this policy.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

OTOGoldMine.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**GOVERNING LAW**

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by India law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Jaipur. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Jaipur, under the rules of Indian Laws. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

OTOGoldMine.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within India. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**CONTACTING US**

We can be reached by clicking [HERE](http://www.otogoldmine.com/support/).
